This is the fastest way to fish,
I'm sure your parents will be happy
that tonight's dinner is taken care of.
You think so?
But I can't control my strength, so
I'm always breaking stuff at home.
And because of that, Mom and Dad get so
embarrassed that they can't help but laugh.
Hey, you gotta look up.
Otherwise you can't choose a product.
What product?
Where did this big, medley box come from?
For some reason, it feels familiar.
Something tells me that this box
is friendly and kind-hearted.
Right, this magic item saved my life.
He's a precious friend of mine.
Don't go, Boxo.
Please take me with you.
Don't leave me all alone again.
After you got abducted, she was so
frantic she didn't even stop to sleep.
I didn't know that.
I think this might have
reminded her of an old incident.
Old incident?
It's probably alright
for me to tell you this.
You see, years ago our village was
wiped out during a monster attack.
It was awful.
Lamas and I were among the few survivors.
Both of our parents ended up dying.
Lamas had her blessing then,
but she was too scared to act.
That's why, to this day, she blames herself
for not being able to save everyone.
I remember she used to be too
afraid to even kill the tiniest bug.
And now she's become a
hunter of all things.
I had no idea she went through all that.
If there's anything that I can do
to help her out, I have to try.
Hey, Boxo?
Promise me, we'll always be together.
Of course.
I'll be here for as
long as you'll have me.
believe
and I'm not alone.
It's your memory, and you
can't find a special moment,
but in the meantime, there are
no friends we haven't seen.
It's amazing how I can see
it, and why are you there?
It's amazing that I can't see it.
I'm still waiting for it.
Thank you.
I've decided to stay in this
village for a little while.
Looks like we'll be neighbors.
Hello there.
If you have any questions about how
things work here, feel free to ask.
Sure, I'll be counting on you.
Great, Director Bear asked me to help
with some more reconstruction around town.
I'll see you later. No
problem. Have fun, I guess.
Miss Hulemy, Mr.
Boxo, we need a favor.
Aren't these guys Suori's bodyguards?
What's going on?
Later today, Mr.
Suori intends to approach the two
of you with a personal request.
We'd like to ask that you hear
what she has to say and then agree.
Wait a second.
You want us to say yes before we
even know what she's asking for?
What do you mean she's already nearby?
Please keep our conversation a secret.
She'd skin us alive if she
found out we were here.
Hey, seriously?
Um, excuse me?
Are you the famous magic
item engineer, Hulemy?
Sorry, I didn't mean to interrupt you.
Yeah, that would be me.
What's your name?
You may...
I mean, my name is Suori.
Please forgive my rudeness, but I have
a matter I need your help dealing with.
Stand up.
You don't have to do
stuff like that, okay?
Enough with the bowing. Oh, yes.
Does that mean you'll accept my request?
I didn't say that, but if you
tell me more, I will consider it.
Very soon, there's going to
be an important gathering.
Influential merchant
families will be showing off
their magic items and
engineers and their employee.
Ah, that explains why you
had your eye on me and Boxxo.
Yes.
I know the girl who planned the event.
Her name is Kanashi, and she's from a
rival merchant family with ties to my own.
Just the thought of her annoying
face is enough to make me scream!
I guess even rich people
have their problems.
Well, it sounds fun.
I could get down to party.
What do you think, Boxo? Hello there!
I guess that decides it, then.
Thank you very much!
Do you have a clear view back there, Boxo?
Hello there!
By the way, where's this girl Suwori
has such a huge grudge against?
From the sounds of it, they
should be close in age.
Ah, there she is.
In terms of who pulls off the
rich girl look, she might win out.
Miss Kanashi!
It's been far too long.
How nice to see you, Miss Suwori.
Please don't feel any
need to put yourself out.
It might be best if
you take your seat now.
That way you'll have the perfect view
from which to watch the proceedings.
You needn't try so hard
yourself, Miss Kanashi.
I'm afraid my conscience
wouldn't be able to handle it
if your little black heart
were to give up from shock.
Is that so?
I wasn't aware you even had a conscience.
It seems your hearing is as
awful as your personality.
Oh, I pity you, my dear.
This is way too mean to be
a conversation between kids.
This person behind you, I'm guessing
she's your magic item engineer?
Yup, that's right!
You see, she's the best around!
Whatever engineer you hired
can't hold a candle to her!
Well then, I'll let you keep up your
confident facade while you still can.
It'll only make the sight of your
miserable frustration all the sweeter.
She makes me so mad!
My apologies.
I'm sorry you had to
see all that ugliness.
Nah, it was actually pretty fun to watch.
Hello there.
Attention, ladies and gentlemen.
We welcome you to this year's event.
We will now begin the
unveiling festivities.
Our first participant.
If you would be so kind, what sort of
magic item did you bring to show us?
This magic item can transform
into a wide variety of weapons.
Oh, I theorized a similar concept
once. This should be good.
Ha!
Well, what do you think?
With this magic item's special ability,
you no longer have to carry
a ton of different weapons?
around with you.
Yeah, that reaction makes sense. Voila!
Is it our turn yet?
I want to get this over with.
This is the moment you've
all been waiting for.
We will now unveil Miss
Kanashi's magic item.
We hope you enjoy the spectacle.
I'm excited to show you the magic
item my engineer brought along.
Feast your eyes on this.
Let's see what you're so proud of.
Eh, whatever it is, I
doubt it's anything good.
This unique magic item was produced based
on the physiology of a certain monster.
Behold, it will obey any command I give.
Is that impossible?
Hold on, no.
To create an intelligent magic item has
long been a dream for all engineers.
And yet, I have accomplished
this nigh impossible feat.
Hey.
Remember what I said
when we got kidnapped?
With our current technology, there's no
way to give a magic item intelligence.
Hello there!
But if you put a person's soul
inside, it's not out of the question.
Though doing so is extremely
dangerous and was declared
illegal by the Magic Item
Engineers Association.
Once, a foolish engineer
thought he was above this rule.
And his hubris destroyed an entire town.
Does that mean we're in danger here?
So, tell me, have you seen anything as
marvelous as this magic item before?
We know who this year's winner will be.
Must kill!
What's this?
You never mentioned it was
capable of human speech.
Shit, I was afraid something
like this would happen.
Must kill!
Wait, what's going on here?
I didn't equip it with a speech function!
I have to shut it down!
This is you who helped me!
How dare you away from my slumber!
That idiot!
He forced a human soul inside
of that magic puppet! Hey, what?
I'm scared!
Hey, you! Shades!
Can you hold that thing down? Ma 'am!
This is it!
Here's the magic seal
keeping the soul in place!
They even put a brainwashing spell on it!
Have some respect for the dead, dammit!
Only way!
I'm sorry.
That must have been torture.
It's not your fault.
You were forced out of your slumber.
Something like this shouldn't
have happened to you.
I promise your rest won't
be disrupted again. No!
How can this be?
I devoted years to
creating that technique.
It was supposed to be
my life's greatest work.
How did you deactivate it so quickly?
You call that crude bit of
engineering your life's work?
What a joke.
With Hulemy on the case, that was easier
than squishing a frog fiend tadpole.
Wait, Hulemy?
You don't mean the girl
wonder of mayhem, Hulemy.
Wasn't she the problem child
at the center of all those
explosions and fires at the
school of magic item engineers?
One time she made a sleeping potion so
strong she put the whole school to sleep.
She made a water purifying drug,
but when she put it in a pond,
it ended up vaporizing the
water instead of purifying it.
You jerks!
Why can't you let that
all stay in the past?
It's such a shame.
Looks like your magic item
engineer just wasn't good enough.
Oh brother, things got a
little hairy for a moment,
but everything turned
out all right in the end.
If you ask me, this
counts as a job well done.
Well, I do have one minor complaint.
I get the feeling that everyone's
totally forgotten about me!
Lately, it started snowing in the village.
It seems that Winter has finally
come to the Clear Flow Lake Stratum.
Everyone, thank you for
gathering here today.
I never would have imagined their
reach would extend this far.
Yeah, I guess we got too complacent.
They've taken control of 70 % of
the strata they've been released in,
and now they've set their sights
on the Clear Flow Lake Stratum.
We have to mount a counterattack,
otherwise we'll be ruined.
We must set aside our
differences and come together.
We will join hands in order to eliminate
the worst threat we've ever faced,
Chains Restaurant! Hear, hear!
At this rate, our
businesses will go under.
I'd rather die than lose my shop.
I've taken the liberty to invite a
certain someone to be our secret weapon.
Would you mind saying hello
to the group? Hello there!
Thank you for joining us today, Boxo.
Based on everything I've gathered so far,
it seems a big-time restaurant chain has
set its sights on our little village.
This chain's restaurant poses an
existential threat to local businesses.
I'll be frank.
We've been driven into a corner and
we're running out of options here.
Damn that greedy chain's restaurant.
At this rate, I won't be
able to feed my children.
How are we supposed to
survive through the winter?
I know why they invited me today.
As ridiculous as it sounds,
they're expecting a
vending machine to figure
out a way to get them
out of this situation.
Please, Boxo, would you be willing to
lend us a hand through this crisis?
If you agree to help,
I promise to let Llamas
stay at the end for
half price once it's back up and running.
If it'll help Llamas out,
there's no way I'll refuse.
Hello there.
Thank you very much.
I'm glad everyone's excited, but
we're not out of the woods yet.
Oh man, I guess I better get
Llamas and Hume on board too.
Attention!
Come one, come all!
Whatever you're craving, we have it!
We here at Chains Restaurants are proud
to offer delicious food at a great price!
This place is super busy, huh?
I'd heard stories about it,
but it's all the more impressive
getting to see it up close like this.
I get why Munami and the
others are concerned.
You guys aren't here to
gather intel, are you?
Nice to meet you.
How did you sniff us out so fast?
You think it might be
the big box on your back?
You must be the intelligent magic
item I've heard so much about.
Would you ever consider coming
over and working for us?
I promise you'll be treated well.
There's no way Boxo would want
to work at a place like that.
Plus, he said he'd always stay with me.
Right, Boxo?
Hello there.
See? Nope.
I figured you might say that.
It's no problem.
In a few months, we'll be
raking in the coins anyway.
Well, we're pretty busy
already, so excuse me.
It's fine i guess tastes pretty
much like i imagined i'd say it's
average at best i wonder if maybe
it's because i'm too used to boxo's
food but the stuff they serve here
doesn't even come close to impressing
me same for me feels like their
flavors are weak that makes sense.
In this world, seasonings aren't
cheap, so things tend to taste plain.
I just thought of a way to beat them.
Thank you for coming.
I now call the second Chains Restaurant
Annihilation meeting to order.
Our only chance to beat them is right now,
while Chains is holding
their opening sale.
To prevent our customers
from being lured away,
we'll convince them to stay by
appealing to their stomachs.
For the first step in our plan, we'll
have to develop a brand new menu.
So did everyone bring their trial
dishes it's good to see them so excited?
Hello there so Boxo I'd love to hear
whatever feedback you have about my
new trial dish how exactly do you want
me to do that actually I don't know if
Boxo can even taste the food how about
you let me and Hula me try it we'll
tell you what we think that sounds
good to me why don't you help yourself?
It's good but I think you could make
the flavor just a little bit stronger.
And maybe the sauce could be thicker?
That way it would stick
to the pasta better.
Also,
you could let the pasta absorb more of the
soup when cooking to impart more flavor.
Nice job!
That's some great advice.
I gotta write that down. Hold on.
Um, what is this, Boxo?
Mmm!
It's so delicious!
It's very well seasoned
and the sauce is thick.
It tastes like it's made from milk.
I can use this as a
reference to improve it.
As expected.
She figured out what to do.
Huh? Mr.
Waxo, teach me your ways!
Please, share your wisdom with us!
It's incredible!
The outside is crispy while
the inside is moist and juicy!
This is the best!
We somehow put fruit and
cream inside of the dough!
It's so sweet and delicious!
After sampling the goods,
they were all inspired.
They quickly sprang into action, developing
dishes based on what they just tasted.
Step right up, step right up.
We have a brand new menu for you today.
Our new dish is fried meat and
oil, which locks the flavor inside.
It's sublime experience
you can only find here.
If you're in the mood for something sweet,
you could try a pastry filled
with delicious fruit and cream.
You can even choose what kind of
fruit you want for the filling.
All right, this is where
the real battle starts.
Yeah,
I just hope they can
take back the customers
who already drifted over
to Chain's restaurant.
Mmm, that smells great.
You want to go check it out?
Chain's line is still super long.
Yeah, let's go.
So tasty!
I've never eaten food like this before.
Wow, this is way better than
the stuff they serve at Chain's.
Good!
Thanks to Lamas and Hulemy
sampling the new dishes,
it looks like things are
turning out pretty well.
Aw, I was wondering why the
restaurant wasn't that busy.
We're all out here, huh?
I'm sure you have something to do with it.
I look forward to serving
you again. Damn you!
You'll pay for this!
That serves you right, you jerk.
Okay, we did it!
Armed with their new menus,
all the shops in Munami's group
flourish like never before.
In other news, a month later,
Chain's Restaurant made the decision to
completely withdraw from
Clear Flow Lake Stratum?
due to their plummeting sales.
To be honest, something
doesn't feel quite right.
They threw in the towel so quickly.
I can't help but think
they're up to something.
Hey there, Boxo.
It looks like you've been
busy again. Hello there.
I actually wanted to talk
to you about something.
What do you think about going on
a campaign with us after winter?
Too bad.
You didn't even pretend
to think about it, huh?
Am I really that unpopular?
Hello there!
Kick a man while he's down?
Come on, Boxo, do you treat all
your regular customers this bad?
I mean, we did volunteer to help
you when you were stuck in a jam.
He's right.
With the Menagerie of Fools helping out,
the Hunter Association was able to take out
that gang of thieves without any issues.
Thank you very much!
Oh?
Does that mean you're
starting to warm up to me?
Don't worry, we'd only bring
you along if Llamas agreed to.
There's still plenty of time
before everything thaws.
Do me a favor and think about it.
My feelings are one thing, but the real
question is, what does Llamas think?
The Menagerie of Fools is a
super well-known group, you know.
Most people would be ecstatic if they
got the opportunity to accompany them.
Yet, you're awfully quiet, Llamas.
I want to be able to keep on fighting.
I'll never get any stronger if I spend
all my time in the safety of the village.
You still haven't given up
on getting revenge, huh?
I suppose it doesn't matter what I say.
Anyway, you've found yourself
a reliable partner now.
Hello there!
Thank you both, Boxxo, Hulemy.
Lamas has been keeping this
pain inside her this whole time.
Despite that, she's always so kind to me.
Even though I can't talk,
I can still do this.
Whoa!
I've never seen flowers
as pretty as these.
It's beautiful.
Is this for me? Hello there!
Look at that.
That's so sweet.
Thanks so much, Boxo!
I'll treasure it forever!
Did you know, Lamas?
In the language of flowers, the
pink carnation symbolizes gratitude.
That's why
I'm so
happy.